One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Grand Line
Momoiro Island (Kamabakka Kingdom)
What is this place?
And more importantly...
What is with these guys!?
Damn it...
Dear Nami-san, Robin-chan...
Are you doing well?
I can't wait to see you again.
When I do, I'm sure we'll become great friends.
grow, grow and grow much stronger! (Yeah!)
The Underwater Prison Impel Down
I wanted you and Luffy to become great marines...
Nevermind marines, you two brothers have become notorious outlaws.
I'm sure you've heard the rumors about Luffy, too.
In Water 7, he picked a fight with the World Government...
and somehow managed to invade the Judicial Island, Enies Lobby.
Oh, yeah. I also told Luffy about his father.
He was really surprised to hear he had a father.
Doesn't matter...
Whether we know about it or not...
as annoying as it is,
both me and Luffy carry the blood of a world-renowned criminal.
There's no way we could have ever been marines.
Even though I owe my mother a debt of gratitude and took the name "Portgas"...
I still can't stand the thought that I carry the blood of that worthless father of mine.
I don't remember him at all, and I don't owe him anything.
Yeah, I get what you mean, but he was just...
That's why...
Gramps...
I'd hate to see you die right now, kid.
Take my name and roam wild and free over the seas!
Become my son!
My old man is...
Whitebeard, and no one else.
Vice Admiral Momonga!
We've spotted a pirate ship.
Whose ship is it?
I know I've seen that mark before...
I'll go look into it right away!
If you can't remember it offhand,
then it can't be anyone important.
Just ignore it.
We must get to our destination quickly.
Yessir!
There's one! A giant Sea-King!
If that thing spots us, it'll swallow the ship whole!
Please don't look this way...
It's gone.
W-We've gotten this far...
but I don't know what good we can do if we continue!
What should we do now, Big Sis Alvida?
Don't look at me.
You were the ones who wanted to come here, right?
You spent so much money on that Eternal Pose, too.
Well, we have to save Captain Buggy, who was taken to Impel Down!
Take a look at the sea.
The Calm Belt lies just beyond here.
That's the monsters' nest.
Do you really think we can make it through with this ship?
The only other route would be to go there on a Navy ship.
The Gates of Justice won't open for a pirate ship, after all.
No way! You mean we can't even get there?
At this rate, Captain Buggy will be put to death!
Along with our new buddy, Ace-kun!
Impel Down is the world's largest prison, which can neither be broken into nor escaped from.
You should just give up already.
This just means that Buggy the Clown's luck as a pirate has run out.
That's not true!
Captain Buggy wouldn't bite the dust from something like this!
He's right! We've sworn to keep following Captain Buggy...
until the day when we finally find what we've been looking for:
Captain John's treasure island!
Richie!
Do whatever you want, then.
I'll take the Big Top, here.
You guys can set off in a rowboat.
No way! This is Captain Buggy's ship!
Buggy isn't here, is he?!
Yeah. You're right...
I know if we go there, we'll all die, so I'm not going.
It'd be a waste to bring the ship there, too.
You guys can just chase after Buggy in a rowboat until you're satisfied.
Yeah!
Well, you'll probably die long before you even see Impel Down.
Captain Buggy! Thank you so much for everything!
We will never forget what you have done for us!
We'll pray that your execution be quick and painless!
Farewell!
Let's meet again in the next life!
This is Momonga.
Marine code G-1 00660.
I will enter the current shortly.
Prepare to open the gates!
Current
location
Mariejois
Navy Headquarters
(Marineford)
Sabaody Archipelago
Enies Lobby
Amazon Lily
The Great Prison
Impel Down
The ship carrying Luffy and Hancock...
is about to enter the current
connecting the three main facilities...
of the World Government...
the Tarai Current, which can only be used by the Navy.
Great Underwater Prison Impel Down
Please, kill me!
Hey! Newbie!
Why are you just sitting there,
munching away at your bread without first greeting the boss of this cell?
It's a rule around here that newbies are supposed to offer their food to the boss!
Learned your lesson yet?
Hey! Wait!
We were just having a small fight!
We ain't on death row!
Let us out!
Four and a half days have passed...
since the departure from
the Island of Women, Amazon Lily.
Vice Admiral Momonga!
The headwind slowed us down a little,
but we've finally reached Impel Down!
This is bad... We have to hurry.
Get Hancock, now!
Yessir!
Hancock-dono! We have arrived!
I will be there shortly.
What's this?
There are more warships here than there were in the Buster Call!
Currently, this is the most dangerous place in the world.
It is obvious that it would be well-guarded.
So, Ace is inside here?
He is probably far below the surface.
Now, hide under my clothes.
Welcome, Vice Admiral Momonga!
L-Look at that!
That's the Pirate Empress!
She's more beautiful than anyone else!
There's no limit to her beauty!
How high can her Beauty Power rise? Ten thousand watts? A million?
What is all the fuss about?
Such a noisy bunch.
May I petrify them?
Please don't.
The Navy doesn't need any more humiliation.
Your condition for helping us was that you wanted to see the man at the center of these events,
Portgas D. Ace, for yourself, right?
I told you before,
but this place is usually strictly off-limits for pirates, even the Seven Warlords of the Sea.
Once you enter,
you will be restrained with Seastone shackles.
You will also have to go through a full body check at the entrance.
We cannot let you free any of the inmates or anything, after all.
Luffy. They will do a body check once we enter.
We'll figure something out. Just keep going!
I do not mind.
What?
Buggy the Clown?!
He's escaped from his cell?!
Is he a Devil Fruit User?
Assistant Warden.
Vice Admiral Momonga and the Warlord Hancock-dono have arrived.
Right. I'll be there in a minute.
She's so cu...uh...open the gates!
Give her whatever service she wants!
Time left until Ace's execution...
33 hours.
Here we go, Luffy.
Do take care!
Hancock-sama! Have a safe trip!
Stop your buzzing, little flies!
Don't be cruel! Take care, now!
Help us!
Help!
What an oppressive atmosphere.
Is this what hell is like?
We have finally made it inside.
We cannot relax yet, however.
I welcome you to my Impel Down!
Ah! My mistake!
Calling it "my" Impel Down is too ambitious!
I am still but the assistant warden, Hannyabal!
Pleasure to meet you!
I'm Momonga.
I've heard what you're here for.
And you must be the Empress, Hancock-dono?
My Empress, Hancock-dono?
Oh, forgive me!
I'm being too ambitious again!
That stinking warden...
Oh! My mistake.
Warden Magellan is in his office down in Level 4.
You will be taken there right now.
Your escorts will be Vice Chief Jailer Domino here, and myself.
It seems you are short on time, so please, come this way.
Vice Admiral, you go over there and undergo your body check.
Our prisoners are all sent into this cage where they are stripped of their clothes...
...and lowered into pots of boiling water.
We call this process the "Lukewarm Bath of Hell".
We use it to "disinfect" and baptize our prisoners, before they are put in their cells.
Even among those prisoners, there are some who are tougher than others.
A few of our recent inmates, Fire Fist Ace...
as well as the Warlord Jinbe, and...
the former Warlord, Crocodile...
...all went through the baptism
without even batting an eyelash.
Here you are.
Guests check in inside this private room.
Don't worry.
Please remove that cloak.
It's the easiest way to conceal someone,
so please hand it over to me.
I have no reason to suspect you,
but if you were thinking of pulling anything suspicious,
we have monitoring Transponder Snails all over Impel Down.
They transmit everything they see to the security monitors.
Well then, first things first.
Put on these Seastone shackles.
I am not even a prisoner, yet I still need shackles...
You are too cautious.
Please, be gentle with me.
What?
You can come out now, Luffy.
That was close!
I thought I'd have to make a break for it when they weren't watching...
You can turn anything into stone, huh?
This seems to be as far as I can take you.
After this, my abilities will be restrained by Seastone.
And you won't be able to hide once they've taken my cloak.
I had hoped to be of more help to you...
What're you saying?
There's no way I'd have made it all the way here by myself!
You got me inside a building surrounded by warships.
You've helped me plenty!
Luffy...
This is a stronghold made to lock people away.
No matter what happens, please do not cause an uproar here.
If you get captured, you will never be able to get out.
Though you are strong, will you promise me to not cause any disturbances?
Right, I got it! I promise!
Thanks a lot, Hancock!
I'll never forget what you did for me!
I'll definitely repay you someday!
Just now... you...
called me...
Hancock?!
Sure thing, Hammock!
Hammock, I want more food!
What's up, Hammock?
Hancock!
Now my life is complete!
Hey, you can turn them back now.
I'll be fine!
This must be... a mutual affection!
They sure are taking their time...
It's a security check, so we have to be thorough about it.
Even those parts...?!
What are you imagining?
Assistant Warden Hannyabal!
The surveillance Transponder Snail isn't transmitting anything...
Is everything all right in there?
Domino! Is something wrong?
The body-check is complete.
The surveillance is working again. No problems.
I am so sorry.
Did that take too long?
Not at all!
No problems here either.
What tasteless treatment of someone who isn't a prisoner...
Just who do you think I am?
Please tolerate it.
It's one of the rules of Impel Down.
This is strange...
My memory feels hazy...
Please lead the way.
As you wish. Head toward the mega-lift over there.
Using this lift, we'll go down to the fourth undersea floor.
That will take us to the Inferno, where Prison Warden Magellan's office is.
I should warn you, it's pretty hot down there.
Luffy?!
I will pray for your fortune.
(Thank you!)
He said "I love you"!
Hey!
H-Hancock-dono! What's wrong?
Be careful with her.
What's this all of a sudden?
Well, now where do I go?
That lift is going down,
and Hancock said Ace was probably at the bottom of the sea...
That's it!
This is what I've got the Vivre Card for.
The Blugori jailers are coming back.
They've secured food.
Open the hatches.
Good job.
Carry the meat to the freezers.
We've found him!
The escaped pirate from Shared Cell 4
in Level 1, Buggy the Clown!
We've confirmed that he's standing in the hall by Isolation Cell 22!
Capture him immediately!
Damn, they found me, huh?
You bastards!
We've lost contact with
surveillance Transponder Snail #71!
Did you hear that? It's Buggy!
Serves him right for trying to escape on his own!
He's got a horrible punishment waiting for him!
There they are! The Blugori!
Go!
Go get him!
The Vivre Card is telling me to go down here, but...
It's a dead end, huh?
Prisoner number 8200.
What? We're not letting him get away!
They've verified him as a Devil Fruit user!
Don't forget the Seastone!
Hurry!
We'll split up and surround him!
Right! I'm in!
Hurry!
What's that?
Level 1 - Crimson Floor
Are all these rooms prison cells?
Screams?
Well, whatever. Anyway, I've gotta keep going!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Huh?
Bro! Bro!
What?
Wait a sec!
What're you doing outside the cage?
Huh? What's up?
Outside the cage? I came from the outside...
See ya!
Wait! Don't lie, dammit!
I ain't lying!
Who are you?
You're not a jailer or a torturer, are you?
How come you're outside the cage?!
You sure are noisy!
Oh, right! Do you guys know where Ace is?
Ace?
Ace... you mean...
Fire Fist Ace?
That's right. I wanna save Ace!
Don't be so reckless!
True, I did hear that he'd been sent here...
If he is, then he's probably down in Level 5!
No way you'd be able to get near that place.
It's impossible!
That's where they keep the guys with bounties over a 100 million, ya know!
Level 5?
Anyway, Bro.
Mind going to the jailers' room and stealing the keys?
Yeah! Please, Bro!
Don't you think that it must have been fate that we met here, in this huge world?
What's that?
The Blugori!
Blugori?
Run away, Bro!
They'll kill ya!
What's with these guys?!
To the right!
To the left!
Fools!
Don't look down on the man with the power of the Split-Split Fruit!
Straw Hat?!
Why are you here?!
Oh. Buggy, huh?
Why you... don't screw with me, you lowlife!
You're as cheeky as ever, I see!
I didn't know you were captured, too!
I came here on my own!
I wasn't captured!
What sort of idiot would willingly enter a prison?
Wait, could it be that you heard of my imprisonment...
and came to rescue me?
Like hell!
–Dumbass! I'm getting sick just thinking about it.
–What the hell are you talking about?!
I promised Hancock that I wouldn't cause an uproar here,
but you got me dragged into this!
It's not like I wanted you to get involved!
Well, I just got foiled in
"Buggy's Great Jail-Break Plan"!
Who gives a damn?!
They're coming from the front, too!
Damn it!
Hey! Why are you escaping, anyway?
What're you talkin' about, stupid?!
You don't know the kinds of torture they put me through!
These guys are cold-blooded monsters!
Then you just have to avoid getting caught, right?
W-W-What are you talking about?!
I'm in a hurry!
Come to think of it, I guess I've already caused an uproar.
That's the thing I can't stand about you and that Red-Hair...
You're always thinking positively, but in a bad way.
Fine. Let's do this!
We'll just have to do it, won't we?!
Time for a great, flashy...
change of plans!
Agreed!